<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CS Society</title>
    <description>The official CS Society of Ashoka University</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 20:06:07 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 20:06:07 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hacktoberfest@Ashoka 2021</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us this &lt;strong&gt;Sunday (17th October 2021)&lt;/strong&gt; for our Hacktoberfest Introductory Session. 
Following the success of last year, we are back with more events and eminent guest speakers from the FOSS Community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt; (October 17th&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;7:00PM - 9:00PM IST)&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Welcome&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Networking&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hacktoberfest 2021 Overview&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduction to Open Source&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Guest Speakers (To be announced soon!)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Workshop: Version Control (Git anf Github)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us with &lt;a href=&quot;meet.google.com/jmz-hgea-mkr&quot;&gt;Google Meet&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hacktoberfest is a month-long celebration of open source software run by DigitalOcean. It consists of a challenge that encourages people to contribute to any open source projects. The first 70,000 participants to complete the challenge will receive a bunch of free SWAG, including a limited edition Hacktoberfest t-shirt as a reward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Official Hacktoberfest website: (https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/hacktoberfest-2021/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/hacktoberfest-2021/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dev</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Core Inductions!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Computer Science Society is gearing up for it’s biggest update yet - we’re fixing some bugs, adding some features, and above all, striving to make the CS Society a more inclusive and more enjoyable experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But before we get to that, we recognized the need to expand our voice, to create a more diverse body of members, so that the new update is representative of you! Hence, we are opening inductions to The Computer Science Society’s Core Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each of the three wings has their own core team that together make up the Society’s Core Team. The three wings are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Development and Machine Learning&lt;/strong&gt; - Join us to help plan and conduct workshops and events aimed at learning new languages, platforms and developing new applications. Current Leadership: Tanvi Roy (PoC), Soham De&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Structures and Algorithms&lt;/strong&gt; - Rebranded from the earlier Competitive Programming Wing, join us to plan discussions and training events for technical interviews and international programming competitions. Current Leadership: Akshat Singh, Vibodh Nautiyal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CS Research&lt;/strong&gt; - If reading research papers, and learning about new advancements in the field of Computer Science is for you, join the CS Research wing, where we’ll organize reading sessions and conduct independent research on exciting themes. Current Leadership: Manish Rajani (PoC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;!--
### Application Form

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdtQyZK9fUnLaOnWQi_L0lo9dClUPsb4gF3hF0mFYQYlg6PlQ/viewform?embedded=true&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Loading…&lt;/iframe&gt;
--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note, while you are welcome to be a member of as many (or all) of the wings, we would recommend you to opt for leadership in only a single department (keeping in mind your time constraints).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt; Inductions have conducluded and we’re very happy to welcome a very talented group of people to the core of the CS Society! We wish them the best and look forward to working with them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/core-inductions-2021/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/core-inductions-2021/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Annual Report</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This year was a big one for the CS Society at Ashoka University. Not only did it come out of dormancy, but the society was finally able to formalise itself into an active academic society. We share the report here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;rebirth&quot;&gt;Rebirth&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add a bunch of emo stuff here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;report&quot;&gt;Report&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;/assets/files/report2020.pdf&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/annual-report-2020/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/annual-report-2020/</guid>
        
        <category>OAA</category>
        
        <category>Events</category>
        
        <category>Society</category>
        
        
        <category>OAA</category>
        
        <category>Report</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alumni Connect - S1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Alumni Connect is a series of roundtables organised by the CS Society to bring together current undergraduates and CS Alumni from Ashoka. This is a highly anticipated event, where students get to interact with their seniors, often after years and is also very inspiring for everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CS alumni panelists for this edition are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Archit Checker&lt;/strong&gt; is a Software Engineering Fellow at AmuseLabs. While at Ashoka, he interned in CO-Sys and TCPD. He has also interned at Lehigh University, USA.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barun Parruck&lt;/strong&gt; is a Software Developer at Google. He plays chess, is an accomplished pianist and types very fast. During his UG he also interned at Microsoft which he converted to a PPO.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nishka Dasgupta&lt;/strong&gt; is a Research Fellow at MSR India, working in SMPC. During her UG days, she has interned at TIFR and NTU, Singapore. She has also been an Outreachy Intern.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preetha Datta&lt;/strong&gt; is a Software Developer at Groww. Prior to this, she was a ML developer at Ceretai Stockholm and a Research Assistant at Aalto University, Finland. While at Ashoka, she had also interned at Cashfree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/alumni-connect/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/alumni-connect/</guid>
        
        
        <category>society</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring CS Research with Prof Debayan</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This session was organized by the Research Wing of the Computer Science Society on the 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of February, 2021. This was an informative session for the entire student body by Professor Debayan Gupta, Assistant Professor at Ashoka University, about how Computer Science research works at Ashoka. Professor Debayan also talked about interdisciplinary research and its importance in the current day. It was an hour long session with 70+ attendees. If you wish to watch the recording of this session, email us on cs.society@ashoka.edu.in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-cs-research&quot;&gt;About CS Research&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research is something that’s often interpreted as boring and intimidating. This session was organized solely for the purpose of helping it become more accessible to student, promoting the idea that “research is for everyone”. This session also helped debunk several myths the students had, like the fact that students in their first year cannot participate in CS Research while actually, they can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;research-wing&quot;&gt;Research Wing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research wing of the CS society works on organizing events like this and conducting several other projects, ranging from facilitating research to organizing reading groups. The membership for the research wing is open: one can simply join the WhatsApp group where all the announcements are made. &lt;a href=&quot;mailto: cs.society@ashoka.edu.in&quot;&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; us for more info!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/cs-research-debg/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/cs-research-debg/</guid>
        
        
        <category>research</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A User's Tutorial to LaTeX</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;LaTeX is often made to seem more complicated than it really is. But what is it really? LaTeX is a:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Document Preparation System&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It’s kindof a programming language for documents&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It’s pronounced &lt;em&gt;Lay-tech&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Lah-tech&lt;/em&gt; not &lt;em&gt;Lay-teks&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It’s not WYSIWIG (What You See is What You Get)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why should any of us use LaTeX? In one word, it’s &lt;strong&gt;control&lt;/strong&gt;. With Office Productivity software like Microsoft Office Word, &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; you can make a pretty document, but you can’t create a header with pre-programmed author names, automatically updating dates and custom styling (or maybe you can, but then you’ll have to use your mouse and click through a bunch of different menus looking for the right setting, and then something will go wrong, and then you’ll try something else… and the list goes on and on).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if there’s ever anything that you can’t do using LaTeX, not to worry! LaTeX has modules and packaages that you can install and import, that do all sorts of things for you - from predefined algorithm notations, coloured code outputs, even coordinate-based diagram drawing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;so-how-do-we-get-started-with-latex&quot;&gt;So, how do we get started with LaTeX?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there’s a bunch of things you could do. You could go the fancy way and install a LaTeX editor on your computer (TexMaker on Windows, MacTeX on OSX), or you could go the easy way and use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.overleaf.com&quot;&gt;Overleaf&lt;/a&gt; - which is what we’re going to do because we’re lazy and this is fast!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/overleaflogin.png&quot; alt=&quot;Logging in on Overleaf&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty easy to use their interface to quickly build your first LaTeX document - be it your Discrete Math assignment, or the next ground-breaking research paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hmm-im-not-sure-im-quite-there-yet&quot;&gt;Hmm, I’m not sure I’m quite there yet…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s okay, here’s a brief overview of what all is there:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preamble
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Packages - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\usepackage{packagename}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Document Type - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;\documentclass&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;article|book&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Other Metadata - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\title{Sample}&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\author{CS Society}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Body
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Environments
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;These are basically enclosed spaces that have a specific output format. They have a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\begin&lt;/code&gt; and an &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\end&lt;/code&gt; (like most living things).&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Examples
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Math (Inline) - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;$(a + b)^2 = a^2 + b^2 + 2 \cdot a \cdot b$&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Math (Multiline) - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\begin{align*} ... \end{align*}&lt;/code&gt; (The * omits automatic line numbering, if you simply do &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\begin{align}&lt;/code&gt; each line will have a number)&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Numbered Lists - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\begin{enumerate} \item ... \item ... \end{enumerate}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Bullet Lists - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\begin{itemize} \item ... \item ... \end{itemize}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Tables - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\begin{tabular}{| c | c | c |} ... \end{tabular}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Commands
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Formatting, alignment, all sorts of other fun things:&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Examples
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bold&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\textbf{Bold}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Italics&lt;/em&gt; - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\textit{Italics}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Underline - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\underline{Underline (This document wasn't written in LaTeX unfortunately)}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Section - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\section{Section Name}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Section (Unnumbered) - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\section*{Unnumbered Section Name}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Math Symbols - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\int \sum \prod \times \cdot \infty&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Math Exponents - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\sqrt[n]{a} A^{20}_{10}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Math Fractions - &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\frac{10}{20}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;okay-i-got-this-whats-next&quot;&gt;Okay, I got this, what’s next?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you’ve covered the basics, what remains is to get good, and then do the fancy pro-stuff. Here’s some stuff to get started:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.overleaf.com/learn/latex/Bibliography_management_in_LaTeX&quot;&gt;Bibliography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.overleaf.com/learn/latex/LaTeX_Graphics_using_TikZ:_A_Tutorial_for_Beginners_(Part_1)%E2%80%94Basic_Drawing&quot;&gt;Diagrams using TikZ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.overleaf.com/latex/templates&quot;&gt;Templates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://latexresu.me/&quot;&gt;Make a Stylish LaTeX Resume&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.markdownguide.org/&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; - All the blogs on this website were written on Markdown, another popular (but less powerful) typesetting format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thats-a-lot-to-keep-track-of-isnt-it&quot;&gt;That’s a lot to keep track of, isn’t it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It sure is! That’s why there’s a whole bunch of different LaTeX cheatsheets available online that list the most commonly used environments, commands and packages. Here’s a few that might be useful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wch.github.io/latexsheet/&quot;&gt;Winston Chang’s Cheatsheet&lt;/a&gt; - Geared towards Scientific Papers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://people.cs.umass.edu/~freedman/resources/Freedman_LaTeXCheatSheet.pdf&quot;&gt;University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/a&gt; - A Super Brief, Yet Super Awesome, LaTeX Cheat Sheet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have fun creating many many pretty documents in the future!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/latex/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/latex/</guid>
        
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        <category>dev</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Machine Learning without Code</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This workshop was conducted as a preliminary introduction to Machine Learning, without any prerequisite knowledge of Programming, Statistics or Calculus. This isn’t a formal gateway or introduction to the field, but a nosedive into deep-learning, involving a hands-on project. In under 60 minutes, the workshop participants gained a high-level understanding of how machines learn and built their first image classifier (using Google’s Teachable Machines).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-machine-learning&quot;&gt;What is Machine Learning?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machine learning focuses on the use of data and algorithms to imitate the way that humans learn. Atleast that was the motivating idea when it started. Machine Learning falls under the larger umbrella of Artificial Intelligence (AI) which concerns machines that are capable of doing tasks requiring ‘human intelligence’. The following illustration should help illustrate this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/ml-venn.png&quot; alt=&quot;Logging in on Overleaf&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-machines-learn&quot;&gt;How do Machines learn?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process of supervised machine learning can be broadly broken down into 3 distinct steps (following &lt;a href=&quot;https://ischoolonline.berkeley.edu/blog/what-is-machine-learning/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; example from UC Berkeley):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Decision Process:&lt;/strong&gt; In general, machine learning algorithms are used to make a prediction or classification. Based on some input data, which can be labelled or unlabeled, your algorithm will produce an estimate about a pattern in the data.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An Error Function:&lt;/strong&gt; An error function serves to evaluate the prediction of the model. If there are known examples, an error function can make a comparison to assess the accuracy of the model.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Model Optimization Process:&lt;/strong&gt; If the model can fit better to the data points in the training set, then weights are adjusted to reduce the discrepancy between the known example and the model estimate. The algorithm will repeat this evaluate and optimize process, updating weights autonomously until a threshold of accuracy has been met.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;challenges-in-todays-machine-learning&quot;&gt;Challenges in today’s Machine Learning&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;privacy&quot;&gt;Privacy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2016, European Union passed the GDPR to protect the personal data of people in the European Union and European Economic Area. Some US states are also developing policies, such as the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), which require businesses to inform consumers about the collection of their data. This recent legislation has forced companies to rethink how they store and use personally identifiable data (PII). This affects the availability of data for training Machine Learning models. This problem gave birth to an active area of research in Privacy-Preserving Machine Learning&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bias-and-discrimination&quot;&gt;Bias and Discrimination&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In their effort to automate and simplify a process, Amazon unintentionally biased potential job candidates by gender for open technical roles, and they ultimately had to scrap the project. Many similar events have raised other pointed questions around the use of AI within hiring practices, such as what data should you be able to use when evaluating a candidate for a role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bias and discrimination aren’t limited to the human resources function either; it can be found in a number of applications from facial recognition software to social media algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;accountability&quot;&gt;Accountability&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since there isn’t significant legislation to regulate AI practices, there is no real enforcement mechanism to ensure that ethical AI is practiced. The current incentives for companies to adhere to these guidelines are the negative repercussions of an unethical AI system to the bottom line. To fill the gap, ethical frameworks have emerged as part of a collaboration between ethicists and researchers to govern the construction and distribution of AI models within society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;workshop-slides-and-recordings&quot;&gt;Workshop Slides and Recordings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;/assets/files/ml1.pdf&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recordings are availabe on the CS Society drive (shared internally)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ml-without-code/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ml-without-code/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting Competitve with Coding</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/into-to-cp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/into-to-cp/</guid>
        
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        <category>cp</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring Open-Source with Hacktoberfest</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hacktoberfest 2020 is a month-long event powered by DigitalOcean, Intel, and DEV to promote the culture of open-source software. In our workshop this Sunday ‘Introduction to Git and GitHub’, you’ll be learning all about Version Control and be prepared to start contributing to the open-source community! If you actively contribute to public repositories in October (and we’ll teach you all of this!), you’ll be getting a free Official Hacktoberfest T-Shirt from DigitalOcean and many more developer swags!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to this, we highly recommend attending our introductory workshop (open to all Ashokans), which is officially recognized by DigitalOcean and listed here. All workshop attendees will also get access to official Hacktoberfest resources, cheatsheets, and goodies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/hacktoberfest-2020/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/hacktoberfest-2020/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dev</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
